Now, little by little, gently, you will begin to make contact by placing
your thumbs slightly in the direction of the ventricles.
With a light hand, good contact with your elbows, and
good contact with your...
Let your whole body and mind serve you.
For your patient.
The thumbs should be light.
You need a homogeneous hand, if possible.
You shouldn't feel too much pressure above or below.
So, open your hands wide, wide, wide.
And first,
try to visualize the space.
Around you, around your patient.
You always work with
this field
around the patient.
Even if you go inside,
you must be spacious in your mind,
spacious in the system.
Even if you
enter the tissue,
you still give
this notion of space.
There is always a need for space.
Embryonic force needs space to express itself.
It needs growth and space.
And now you place your hands and feel like
a thread rising from your hands.
Towards your brain, you feel, there,
as everything opens well, you feel a connection from your hands
to your brain, you let
your brain be there, the power of your brain, you trust
your receptors, you trust your hands.
You try to perceive well, to distinguish the
first layer which is hair, or not.
It's about feeling this hair with your fingers.
You create a map in your mind.
There, this is the frequency of hair, that's easy.
It's the visible layer, you see.
And then, little by little,
you feel that the hair is attached to the skin.
You focus more on the skin.
You try
not to move.
You try not to move.
In your perception, just in the feeling.
And there, you already sense the difference between this first layer and the skin.
And now, you will gradually enter,
with your field, you enter gently,
to now feel the bony structure,
the outer bone,
the hair, the skin
which is itself attached to the bone,
surrounding the bone.
You place yourself on the bone.
You try to feel the difference.
On the outer cortex.
Then with a little time, you focus,
you feel that you can go a little deeper.
Another density will emerge, another...
You enter inside, you pass through gently.
To feel what is happening behind the bone.
There you reach something more
fluidic.
You went from hair to skin, to
bone,
the inner part, then you go inside.
There you still have...
It's still a layer that is somewhat what we call the parietal layer
of the dura mater.
You use the warmth of your hands to inform
your receptors.
The liquid side up there, the
extracerebral compartment.
You go further down in your perception.
To join the very thin membranes.
Perfect for us to go.
That layer is mostly the most superficial layer.
Now, you gently enter, gradually into the...
The brain emits electricity, it’s an interface that you feel.
It's a different frequency, it's a bit more electric,
tingling.
And now you descend, gently further, towards
the ventricular plane.
You cross the different layers like grey matter,
white matter, towards the central nuclei.
You go down, you apply yourself, you focus,
you concentrate on your thumbs to have
the
ventricles.
There, you feel that the right hemisphere and the left hemisphere
have slightly separated movements.
Thank you for watching this video!
It accompanies the ventricle like a dolphin swimming ahead
and then the other hemisphere with a slight delay and lag.
It doesn't breathe at the same speed.
You play, you let yourself be guided.
And when you return layer by layer, ventricle,
then you go to the level of the nuclei
central.
white matter, the cortex, the
bimeda, the epidural layer, the arachnoid,
the dura mater,
the inner cortex, the future tube is
the outer cortex, the face, the dura mater,
the skull, and the skin, and then the presence at the level of the hair.
Okay, it’s all good, it’s all good.
Subtitles in FR?